# Vergil Kelley

(708)973-9694

verg\_1@yahoo.com

# **Professional Summary**

I am a native Chicagoan well trained, self-taught web developer that knows how to create and modify web content using responsive design techniques. Experienced in analyzing customer needs, working with teams using software for manipulating multimedia content and possess the capacity to learn and adapt in a fast paced environment.

# **Technical Skills**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- PHP/MySQL
- Bootstrap 4
- Git/GitHub
- Atom
- Sublime
- Visual Studio Code
- WordPress
- Windows 10

Experience

2017 - Present

### Front-end Web Developer

### Freelance, Chicago II

Versatile Front-end Developer offering web development services to individuals and small businesses. Creating clean, precise, cross-browser compatible code using responsive technologies like Bootstrap, CSS Grid and Flexbox. Collaborating with end-users to find creative and innovative solutions for exceptional UI/UX.

2015 - Present

### Doorman

# Burnham Park Plaza, Chicagi Il

Opening the front doors politely and greeting residents and guests with cordial professional verbage. Announce guests, observe security cameras and maintain a general cleanliness in and around the front-desk and entry-way to the building.

2010 - 2014

## **Food Delivery**

# Pizano's Pizza, Chicago II

Successfully navigating the Chicago downtown area to deliver food products in a timely fashion, ensuring freshness and overall quality while providing outstanding customer service.

2000 - 2009

# **Real Estate Investor**

## Self employed, Chicago II

Buying, selling and leasing of residential single family and multi-unit properties in the Chicagoland area. Conducted market analysis of forclosed homes and marketed vacant units. Prepared rental agreements, ensuring accuracy and completion. Performed general property management functions including supervising construction crews.

Education

### Roosevelt University, Chicago Illnois

Accounting and Business Management (6 credit hours)

### Northeastern Illinois University, Chicago Illinois

Accounting and Business Management (84 credit hours)